It has happened
[Music]
Om Om
Ajay has happened
[Music] It has happened
[Music]
that do it
All the businesses, jobs and
all your means of livelihood are closed in Jhaal, in such a situation if we have to
spend a few lakh rupees in the hospital due to some illness,
then what will affect our financial condition a lot,
according to all the media reports the real danger of
corona will start when people open up, when all of us get out of the trap,
if you do
not take a health policy today, then even when the lockdown is exhausting, you will
not have any security, just
think if today, despite having money, we are avoiding paying the premium of
ten to twenty thousand rupees for the health policy, then
how much pain will we face if we have to pay a few lakh rupees, today in the race of lockdown
we
are all ready to buy food and water online, but we do not have time to think that health insurance
policy is available at home,
so do not get it done today,
take Quote 24 policy and save your business or
savings from going to the hospital, let
us get the turmeric done today, Hello once again a very warm
welcome to our YouTube
channel, in today's video we  We
will compare the subscription between 2019 and
ICICI Lombard, so please watch this video
because in this video I will
give you information and those who are associated with this game
can also subscribe, so let's
start, first of all
we will know what is the difference between these plans,
what are the things that
make these plans different from each other, first of all we will
talk about all the options, if you have not subscribed to the company from 3 lakh
to 100, then
I will tell you to subscribe for only 2 lakh to 50, then you can
subscribe for 3000 rupees and you will get up
to 1500 rupees for road show,
modern dollar, you get help from
wrestler, you are covered, at this time you
are covered for shot and virus, and liptis
and the limit has been mentioned, you
only get organ donor expenses for two adults,
where there is news,
now we will talk about no claim bonus,
friends, Max Bupa Health Compensation
Language, you get a bonus of 20 per cent
of them  Inside every year, the maximum which
goes up to 100%, that juice
never reduces in Max Bupa,
even after taking the same iron plant, you get the
benefit of bonus, you get additional
commission top ten percent every oil olive oil,
which goes up to a maximum of only 50%
and there is also this advantage here, this phone
which time to celebrate is used
on our,
you get hospital cash on Kevin Fee,
which help them in this, you get
₹1000 per day to ₹4000 and
in the exam you get ₹500 on options leaving near two lakhs, you
get ₹1000 on options review up to 3, 4, 5 lakhs and
you get ₹1000 on options by
clearing ₹2000 and
on all the introductions from 15 to 50 lakhs,
you get hospital cash up to ₹3000 here
Max Bupa Health in the app for health
checkup
You get a free health check-up on Thursdays and in Iron Plant, you get a free health check-up on every
politician.
Friends, we have talked about the difference between these plants.
Now we will talk about the
cases in which these treatments are available in Express.
So you have to
subscribe to the districts.
Now let's talk about the treatment cover. In
both the classes, you have the
treatment cover up to 7 minutes and the relative
treatment is the best in the country. You get the
facility of Life From Real.
You get tax benefits. You get a
15-day free look
period for STDs. You get the cancellation facility.
Now we will talk about those benefits which
you get only in Bupa Health Comment.
Today, that great benefit of deductible is available to you.
Answer option is available from ₹1 lakh to ₹10,
for example, weekly addition expenses. If
you are aware then Jasmine Shirt, now we will talk
about the refill benefits
friends.  Maths is uncle, in this company Pran
you get health benefit hundred
percent of this mixture that
after accessing the sum in your policy you
cannot use simple spray on the minute.
Talking about OPD cover,
in OPD you get animal back cover recharges
from Rs.2500 to Rs.7000. Now let's
talk about those benefits which you get
only in I hospital.
You get event and preventive health care benefit from Rs.2500
to Rs.1000. You definitely get some modern options
like you get critical illness cover
and maximum total time which is
three-four parts of and in 10 lakh plans
you get hundred percent of this
mixture and in plans from 15 to 50 lakh
you get 50 percent of dissemination of
information systems benefit you get
₹10 per day. If you send some submissions
to the helpline, you get cutter's benefit  In the treatment,
you will have to pay 20 thousand rupees for eye treatment but for
lipid it comes only if your income is 2 to 5
lakhs then there is a
possibility of 10 lakhs in Islam. You do
not get any submission in Islam
that some value added services are given to you, it is
free checkup coupon,
maximum two-thirds of which you get
online chat with medical practitioners,
you get the facility of special IT extolation,
you get the explanation of a consultant on diet and nutrition,
now we will talk
about implanted implants which are almost the same in implants, the
initial waiting period prevents this, for this
you have a waiting period of 24 months
and for West Indies you
get marks and you have a waiting period of 24 to 48 months.
Hello friends, this was a little information about
Max Bupa Help Them In and ICICI
Lombard IS implanted implants.
Please tell me through comments how
you liked this video, if you have any question
in your mind related to this video then
Ask in the comments if you really like this video then
definitely share this video with your relatives on WhatsApp, this will
help them and you will get benefit,
don't forget to subscribe to the channel, like the video, keep it up
and I
bring such informative videos for you so that
you can keep getting more information from my videos, first of all thank you
for watching my video
Ajay ko hua
hai
[music]
do it
Hello friends, pay to health, I
think about you, you can type this and
design your website,
so friends, in today's video
we will go over how you can select the roads of your fans,
today we will talk
about Ray, Papa Francis Ram, he has
happened